Guide to the John Franklin Enders Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence and Topical Files, 1916-1988; Series I; 36.75' (88 boxes)
  - Equipment
    - Fish-spine beads: Dr. Porterfield, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 502)
    - Flow Laboratories, 1962, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 503)
    - Grand Island Biological Company, 1964-1968 (Box 22, Folder 504)
    - Hamsters, 1947, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 505)
    - Harris Manufacturing Company, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 506)
    - Heinicke Instruments Company, 1959-1960, 1963, 1968-1969, undated (Box 22, Folder 507)
    - Hoke-Phoenix reducing valve, undated (Box 22, Folder 508)
    - Ice Pak International, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 509)
    - Instructions and guarantees, 1942, 1946, 1949-1951, 1955, undated (Box 22, Folder 510)
    - Ivan Sorvall, Inc.: centrifuge, 1953, 1957-1959, 1962, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 511)
    - Kwik-Chek gas analyzer, undated (Box 22, Folder 512)
    - Lab-Line Instruments, Inc., 1964-1966, undated (Box 22, Folder 513)
    - Lab-Tek tissue culture, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 514)
    - Laboratory animals, 1969, undated (Box 22, Folder 515)
    - Labtool Specialties, 1961-1967, undated (Box 23, Folder 516)
    - Linbro Chemical Company, 1955, 1967, undated (Box 23, Folder 517)
    - Massey Dickinson Co., 1959, undated (Box 23, Folder 518)
    - Meems Bros. & Ward:, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 519)
    - Metalab Equipment Company, 1961, undated (Box 23, Folder 520)
    - Microbiological Associates, Inc., 1957 (Box 23, Folder 521)
    - Microscope and lamp cameras, 1966, undated (Box 23, Folder 522)
    - Microtiter: Intercontinental Scientific Corp., 1961, undated (Box 23, Folder 523)
    - Microtiter kit and calibrated pipette droppers: Cooke Engineering Co., 1961-1962, undated (Box 23, Folder 524)
    - Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Company, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 525)
    - Northeastern Supply Co.: poultry, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 526)
    - Original equipment for Jimmy Fund building, undated (Box 23, Folder 527)
    - Original equipment for Research Division of Infectious Disease, 1947, 1951, undated (Box 23, Folder 528)
    - Photographic supplies: Joshua Meier Division/W. R. Grace & Co., undated (Box 23, Folder 529)
    - Poultry, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 530)
    - Rabbits, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 531)
    - Rockland Farms, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 532)
    - Royal typewriter, 1964-1965, undated (Box 23, Folder 533)
    - Scientific Glass Apparatus Co., Inc., 1958, 1961-1963, undated (Box 23, Folder 534)
    - Sears, Roebuck and Co.: fan heater, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 535)
    - The Squibb Institute for Medical Research, 1955, 1958-1960, undated (Box 23, Folder 536)
    - T. E. Frothingham Memorial Incubator, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 537)
    - Thompson's Fairweather Farm, 1947, 1954-1956, 1966, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 538)
    - Trefflich's Bird and Animal Co., Inc.: monkeys, 1943-1945 (Box 23, Folder 539)
    - Trefflich's Bird and Animal Co., Inc.: monkeys, 1946-1950, 1957-1964 (Box 23, Folder 540)
    - Unitron Instrument Co., undated (Box 23, Folder 541)
    - Vertical deep freeze, 1958-1959, undated (Box 23, Folder 542)
    - VirTis Company, Inc., 1954, 1957, undated (Box 23, Folder 543)
  - Espangne, Henriette, 1957, undated (Box 23, Folder 544)
  - European Committee on Crime Problems, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 545)
  - Evans, Alfred S., 1946-1949 (Box 23, Folder 546)
  - Evans, Charles A., 1948-1951, 1958, undated (Box 23, Folder 547)
  - Ewalt, Jack R., 1957 (Box 23, Folder 548)
  - Examiner Club of Boston, 1957-1977, undated (Box 23, Folder 549)
  - Exanthema, 1954-1955 (Box 23, Folder 550)
  - Excerpta Medica Foundation, 1946, 1951, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 551)
  - Fabia, Jacqueline, 1965-1966, 1971, undated (Box 23, Folder 552)
  - Faichney, James B., 1962 (Box 24, Folder 553)
  - Fainstat, Theodore, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 554)
  - Farbenfabriken Bayer AG, 1960-1961, undated (Box 24, Folder 555)
  - Farber, Sidney
    See: box 14, folders 295-296
  - Fastier, Lyle, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 556)
  - Favorite, Grant O., 1941-1942 (Box 24, Folder 557)
  - Faxon, Henry H., 1951-1952 (Box 24, Folder 558)
  - Federal Security Agency, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 559)
  - Federation of American Scientists, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 560)
  - Federation of American Societies for Experimental Biology, 1950-1954, 1958, undated (Box 24, Folder 561-562)
  - Feemster, Roy, 1948, 1952-1954 (Box 24, Folder 563)
  - Feingold, David S., 1971, undated (Box 24, Folder 564)
  - Feldman, Harry A., 1972 (Box 24, Folder 565)
  - Feldman, W. H., 1936 (Box 24, Folder 566)
  - Feline panleucopenia, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 567)
  - Feller, A. E., 1941-1947, 1953-1959, 1963, undated (Box 24, Folder 568)
  - Felt, H. D., 1958, 1971, undated (Box 24, Folder 569)
  - Fenner, Frank, 1961-1963, undated (Box 24, Folder 570)
  - Ferrebee, Joseph, 1947-1948, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 571)
  - Ferry, R. M., 1941, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 572)
  - Fessenden School, 1947, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 573)
  - Fewster, Mona E., 1969 (Box 24, Folder 574)
  - Fieser, L. F., 1938 (Box 24, Folder 575)
  - Findlay, G. M., 1950-1951 (Box 24, Folder 576)
  - Finland, Maxwell, 1940-1943, 1948-1956, 1962, 1966, 1972-1974 (Box 24, Folder 577)
  - Finter, N. B., 1955-1956 (Box 24, Folder 578)
  - Fitz, Reginald, 1942-1943, 1948, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 579)
  - Fitzpatrick, Thomas B., 1963 (Box 24, Folder 580)
  - Fiumara, Nicholas J., 1965-1967 (Box 24, Folder 581)
  - Fjelde, Audrey, 1963-1965, 1971, undated (Box 24, Folder 582)
  - Flattery Prize, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 583)
  - Flexner, Simon, 1936 (Box 24, Folder 584)
  - Flick, John A., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 585)
  - Florman, Alfred L., 1942-1949, 1961, 1964, 1968, 1971, undated (Box 24, Folder 586)
  - Fluorescent antibody methody, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 587)
  - Fluoridation, 1956-1959, 1962-1964 (Box 24, Folder 588)
  - Fogh, Jorges, 1960, 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 589)
  - Foley, George, 1942, 1948-1949, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 590)
  - Folkman, Judah, 1970-1975, undated (Box 24, Folder 591)
  - Forbes, John, 1958-1962 (Box 24, Folder 592)
  - Foreign student financial aid, 1959-1961, undated (Box 24, Folder 593)
  - Fothergill, Leroy D., 1946-1949, 1964, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 594)
  - Fox, Charles, 1940-1941 (Box 24, Folder 595)
  - Fox, John P., 1951, 1957-1961, 1971-1972, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 596)
  - Framingham Union Hospital, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 597)
  - Francis, Elaina Thayer, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 598)
  - Francis, Mary Jane, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 599)
  - Francis, Thomas, 1939, 1941, 1948-1949, 1952-1960, 1963-1970 (Box 25, Folder 600)
  - Frank, Samuel B., 1941 (Box 25, Folder 601)
  - Frankel, Jack W., 1958-1960, 1965-1966, 1974, undated (Box 25, Folder 602)
  - Fraser, Dean, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 603)
  - Fraser, K. B., 1961 (Box 25, Folder 604)
  - Frazier, W. L., 1945 (Box 25, Folder 605)
  - French, Eric L., 1974 (Box 25, Folder 606)
  - Freund, Jules, 1938, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 607)
  - Friedheim, E., 1942 (Box 25, Folder 608)
  - Friedlich, Allan L., 1942 (Box 25, Folder 609)
  - Fritz, Michael E., 1970 (Box 25, Folder 610)
  - Frontiers of Science Foundation of Oklahoma, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 611)
  - Frost, S. H., 1942 (Box 25, Folder 612)
  - Frothingham, Thomas E., 1953-1956 (Box 25, Folder 613)
  - Frothingham, Thomas E., 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 614)
  - Frothingham, Thomas E., 1959-1961, 1967-1969, 1972, undated (Box 25, Folder 615)
  - Fulton, John, 1955-1956, undated (Box 25, Folder 616)
  - Funk and Wagnall's Universal Standard Encyclopedia, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 617)
  - Furth, Jacob, 1956-1958 (Box 25, Folder 618)
  - Gajdusek, D. Carleton, 1950-1958, 1961-1967 (Box 25, Folder 619-620)
    See also: box 47, folder 1168
  - Gajdusek, D. Carleton, 1969-1974, 1980, undated (Box 25, Folder 621-622)
  - Galen Medal in Therapeutics, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 623)
  - Gallagher, J. Roswell, 1946, 1949, 1952, 1955, undated (Box 26, Folder 624)
  - Galloway, Ian, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 625)
  - Gamble, James L., 1944-1947, 1951, 1957-1960 (Box 26, Folder 626)
  - Gamble Professorship, 1970, undated (Box 26, Folder 627)
  - Gard, Sven, 1949-1950, 1955, 1964-1965 (Box 26, Folder 628)
  - Gardner, Pierce, 1971, 1976, undated (Box 26, Folder 629)
  - Garland, Joseph E., 1955-1960, 1963-1967 (Box 26, Folder 630)
  - Garland, Mary Anne, 1962, undated (Box 26, Folder 631)
  - Gay, William I., 1970 (Box 26, Folder 632)
  - Gear, James H. S., 1954-1955, 1958-1961, 1967, 1977, undated (Box 26, Folder 633)
  - Gebhardt, Louis P., 1948, 1951-1952, 1961, 1969, 1973, undated (Box 26, Folder 634)
  - Gellis, Sydney S., 1946, 1959-1960 (Box 26, Folder 635)
  - Gente, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 636)
  - Gerald, Park S., 1973-1974, 1977, undated (Box 26, Folder 637)
  - Gerber, Paul, 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 638)
  - German Medical Research, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 639)
  - Gey, George O., 1950-1952, 1961-1962, 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 640)
  - Gezon, Horace, 1948-1949 (Box 26, Folder 641)
  - Giant cell pneumonia, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 642)
  - Gibson, John G., 1972 (Box 26, Folder 643)
  - Ginsberg, Harold S., 1961, 1965-1966, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 644)
  - Giovanardi, Augusto, 1952-1954, 1958-1966, undated (Box 26, Folder 645)
  - Gitlin, David, 1952, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 646)
  - Glaser, Ronald, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 647)
  - Glezen, W. Paul, 1975, undated (Box 26, Folder 648)
  - Globulin
    - Correspondence, 1945-1946, 1950-1955 (Box 26, Folder 649)
    - Janeway's project, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 650)
    - Records, 1945-1950 March-November (Box 26, Folder 651-652)
    - Records, 1950 December-1953, undated (Box 27, Folder 653)
    - Standardization, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 654)
    - Sterilization of plasma, 1952, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 655)
  - Glover, Milton, 1972-1973, undated (Box 27, Folder 656)
  - Goffe, A. P., 1951, 1958-1961 (Box 27, Folder 657)
  - Gohd, Robert S., 1950-1954, 1958, undated (Box 27, Folder 658)
  - Goldblum, Nathan, 1956, 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 659)
  - Goodpasture, Ernest W., 1949 (Box 27, Folder 660)
  - Gordon, Francis B., 1958-1960 (Box 27, Folder 661)
  - Gordon, Irving, 1950, 1954-1955, 1958-1960, 1963-1964, 1967, undated (Box 27, Folder 662)
  - Gordon Conference, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 663)
  - Goss, Leonard, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 664)
  - Gottlieb, Tamar, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 665)
  - Grand Island Biological Company, 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 666)
  - Grant, Lester, undated (Box 27, Folder 667)
  - Grant, Louis S., 1954 (Box 27, Folder 668)
  - Greater Boston Annual Achievement Award, 1957, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 669)
  - Greater Boston Medical Society, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 670)
  - Green, Morris, 1965-1967, undated (Box 27, Folder 671)
  - Green, Robert H., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 672)
  - Green, William T., 1949-1957, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 673)
  - Greer, Joseph P., 1959 (Box 27, Folder 674)
  - Grenier, Bernard, 1956-1959, 1965-1966, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 675)
  - Gresser, Ion, 1959-1979 (Box 27, Folder 676-679)
  - Gresser, Ion, 1981-1983 (Box 27, Folder 680)
  - Gresser, Ion, undated (Box 28, Folder 681-682)
  - Griffith, John F., 1967-1971, undated (Box 28, Folder 683)
  - Grogan, Elizabeth Anne, 1958-1960 (Box 28, Folder 684)
  - Gross, Ludwik, 1963, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 685)
  - Gross, Peter A., 1967-1968 (Box 28, Folder 686)
  - Gross, Robert E., 1951 (Box 28, Folder 687)
  - Groupé, Vincent, 1948, undated (Box 28, Folder 688)
  - Gudakunst lecture, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 689)
  - Gunalp, Altan, 1957, 1961-1966, 1969, undated (Box 28, Folder 690)
  - Habel, Karl, 1946-1947, 1950-1951, 1961, 1964, 1967, undated (Box 28, Folder 691)
  - Hachtel, Frank W., 1944 (Box 28, Folder 692)
  - Haden, R. L., 1938 (Box 28, Folder 693)
  - Hahn, Erich, 1969-1971 (Box 28, Folder 694)
  - Hale, Worth, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 695)
  - Hall, Thomas C., 1968-1969, undated (Box 28, Folder 696)
  - Halonen, Pekka E., 1967 (Box 28, Folder 697)
  - Hamilton, Terrell H., 1961-1962 (Box 28, Folder 698)
  - Hammon, William M., 1939-1949 (Box 28, Folder 699)
  - Hammon, William M., 1952-1964, 1973, undated (Box 28, Folder 700)
  - Handler, Alfred H., 1965-1966, 1971, undated (Box 28, Folder 701)
  - Hanks, John, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 702)
  - Hanna lecture: Western Reserve University School of Medicine, 1956, undated (Box 28, Folder 703)
  - Happold, Edmund, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 704)
  - Harding, Ferdinand R., 1958 (Box 28, Folder 705)
  - Harper, Margaret M., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 706)
  - Harris, Bruce, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 707)
  - Harris, Henry, 1967, 1970-1974 (Box 29, Folder 708)
  - Harrop, George A., 1942 (Box 29, Folder 709)
  - Hartford Hospital, 1951-1953, 1958, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 710)
  - Hartford Medical Society, 1955-1960, 1963, 1966-1967 (Box 29, Folder 711)
  - Hartmann, John R., 1949 (Box 29, Folder 712)
  - Harvard Crimson, 1956-1957, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 713)
  - Harvard Medical Alumni Association, 1948, 1953-1955, 1962-1966 (Box 29, Folder 714)
  - Harvard Medical Alumni Bulletin, 1958, 1961, 1982, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 715)
  - Harvard Medical Society, 1944, 1963-1965, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 716)
  - Harvard University
    - Biological Laboratories, 1957, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 717)
    - Committee on Cancer Research and Training
      See: box 11, folders 239-242
    - Correspondence, general, 1939-1946, 1951, 1954-1956, 1960-1969 (Box 29, Folder 718)
    - Division of Medical Sciences, 1957-1962 (Box 29, Folder 719)
    - John F. Enders University Professorship, 1967, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 720)
    - Medical School
      - Administrative Board, 1942-1946 (Box 29, Folder 721-723)
      - Committee of Professors, 1960, 1963-1965 (Box 29, Folder 724)
      - Committee on Human Reproduction, 1963-1965 (Box 29, Folder 725)
      - Correspondence, general, 1942-1946, 1955, 1959-1969, undated (Box 29, Folder 726-727)
      - Department of Bacteriology and Immunology: lecture schedules, 1948, 1953-1970, undated (Box 29, Folder 728-729)
      - Department of Preventive Medicine, 1957, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 730)
      - Department of Preventive Medicine, 1969-1970, undated (Box 30, Folder 731)
      - Division of Infectious Diseases, 1944-1946, undated (Box 30, Folder 732)
      - Dunham Lectureship Committee, 1947-1954, 1957-1961, 1964-1969, 1972, undated (Box 30, Folder 733)
      - Faculty of Medicine, 1947, 1952, 1959, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 734)
      - Faculty of Medicine, 1964-1965, undated (Box 30, Folder 735)
      - Human Reproduction Center, 1963-1965 (Box 30, Folder 736)
      - New England Regional Primate Research Center, 1963-1967 (Box 30, Folder 737-738)
      - New England Regional Primate Research Center, 1968-1971 (Box 31, Folder 739-740)
      - New England Regional Primate Research Center, 1972 April-December 11 (Box 31, Folder 741)
      - New England Regional Primate Research Center, 1972-1976, undated (Box 31, Folder 742-744)
      - Program for Harvard Medicine, 1961-1965 (Box 31, Folder 745)
      - Tenure committee, 1971-1972, undated (Box 31, Folder 746)
      - Tercentenary Symposium, 1936, undated (Box 31, Folder 747)
    - Monographs in Medicine and Public Health, 1947-1951 (Box 32, Folder 748)
    - School of Public Health
      - Ad hoc committees, 1949, 1955-1960, 1963, 1966, 1969, undated (Box 32, Folder 749)
      - Correspondence, general, 1946, 1953, 1958, 1963-1965, 1969, undated (Box 32, Folder 750)
      - Dean, 1943-1945 (Box 32, Folder 751)
  - Harvard University Press, 1943-1944 (Box 32, Folder 752)
  - Heath, Clark W., 1943 (Box 32, Folder 753)
  - Heffelfinger, F. Peavey, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 754)
  - Heidelberger, Michael, 1936, 1948, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 755)
  - Heineman, H. S., 1966 (Box 32, Folder 756)
  - Hektoen Institute for Medical Research, 1957, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 757)
  - Hench, Philip S., 1950, 1956, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 758)
  - Henderson, L. J., 1941 (Box 32, Folder 759)
  - Henle, Gertrude and Werner, 1946-1951, 1954, 1957-1969, 1973-1975 (Box 32, Folder 760)
  - Henn, Fritz, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 761)
  - Henneman, Philip H., 1946 (Box 32, Folder 762)
  - Hennessen, W., 1957, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 763)
  - Hennings, Thomas C., 1959 (Box 32, Folder 764)
  - Hepatitis
    - Boggs, Joseph, 1969-1970, undated (Box 32, Folder 765)
    - Conrad, Glickman, and Murray, 1968-1970, undated (Box 32, Folder 766)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1957, 1961-1968, undated (Box 32, Folder 767)
    - Laboratory data, notes, etc., 1970-1972, undated (Box 32, Folder 768)
    - Melnick, Joseph D., 1970, undated (Box 32, Folder 769)
    - Papers, 1970, undated (Box 32, Folder 770)
    - Subgroup, 1964-1965 (Box 32, Folder 771)
    - Symposium, 1965, undated (Box 32, Folder 772)
  - Hepatitis Scientific Memoranda, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 773)
  - Hermann, Ernest C., 1970, undated (Box 32, Folder 774)
  - Herpes Simplex, 1946, 1956, 1962-1964, undated (Box 32, Folder 775)
  - Herring, Louis C., 1941 (Box 32, Folder 776)
  - Hertig, Arthur, 1949, 1962, 1966, 1969-1974, undated (Box 32, Folder 777)
  - Hertz, Roy, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 778)
  - Hertzog, Frank, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 779)
  - Heyl, Henry, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 780)
  - Heyl, James T., 1957, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 781)
  - Hiatt, Howard, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 782)
  - Hill, Louis Webb, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 783)
  - Hilleman, Maurice R., 1964-1968 (Box 33, Folder 784)
    See also: box 47, folders 1171-1173 See also: box 56, folder 1327
  - Hilleman, Maurice R., 1969-1975, undated (Box 33, Folder 785-786)
  - Himmelweit, F., 1961-1962, undated (Box 33, Folder 787)
  - Hinton, William A., 1959-1960, 1971, undated (Box 33, Folder 788)
  - Hitchcock Foundation, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 789)
  - Ho, Monto, 1957-1970, 1973-1974, 1978, undated (Box 33, Folder 790-793)
  - Hodes, Horace L., 1947, 1955, 1960, 1969, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 794)
  - Holdaway, David, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 795)
  - Holden, Margaret, 1938, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 796)
  - Holden, Reuben A., 1956 (Box 33, Folder 797)
  - Holland, John, 1962-1963, 1969, undated (Box 33, Folder 798)
  - Holloway, Ann, 1959-1961, 1964-1966, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 799)
  - Holt, Anna, 1957, undated (Box 34, Folder 800)
  - Holton, Gerald, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 801)
  - Hood Foundation: Child Health Award, 1970-1974, undated (Box 34, Folder 802-804)
  - Hooker, Sanford B., 1936, 1939, 1941 (Box 34, Folder 805)
  - Horneff, J. Arthur, 1942, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 806)
  - Hornus, Georges, 1936 (Box 34, Folder 807)
  - Horrax, Gilbert, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 808)
  - Horsfall, Frank L., 1940-1947, 1951-1954, 1957-1958, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 809)
  - Horstmann, Dorothy, 1948, 1955, 1960-1967, 1970-1974, 1981-1982, undated (Box 34, Folder 810-811)
  - Howard, Rutledge W., 1943 (Box 34, Folder 812)
  - Howe, Calderon, 1941-1943, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 813)
  - Howe, Howard A., 1949-1951, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 814)
  - Howes, D. W., 1961 (Box 34, Folder 815)
  - Hsiung, Gueh-Djen, 1968-1969, 1973-1976, undated (Box 34, Folder 816)
  - Huang, Alice, 1969-1970, undated (Box 34, Folder 817)
  - Huang, Helena, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 818)
  - Hubel, David, 1982, undated (Box 34, Folder 819)
  - Huddleson, I. F., 1943 (Box 34, Folder 820)
  - Huebner, Robert J., 1953-1954, 1962-1966, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 821)
  - Hull, Emeral W., 1945 (Box 34, Folder 822)
  - Hull, Robert N., 1958-1959, undated (Box 34, Folder 823)
  - Hurst, E. Weston, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 824)
  - Huxley, Julian, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 825)
  - Ibadan University of Nigeria, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 826)
  - Iceland disease, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 827)
  - Immunity Principles and Applications in Medicine and Public Health, 1945-1947, undated (Box 34, Folder 828)
  - India, letters from, 1945-1947, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 829)
  - Indian Council of Medical Research, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 830)
  - Indiana University, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 831)
  - Industrial Research, Inc., 1967 (Box 34, Folder 832)
  - Infectious Disease Group, 1957, 1960-1964, 1967-1968 (Box 34, Folder 833)
  - Infectious Diseases Society, 1948, 1957, 1961-1965 (Box 34, Folder 834-835)
  - Infectious Diseases Society, 1966-1968, 1972, undated (Box 35, Folder 836)
  - Influenza vaccine, 1946-1947, 1957-1958, 1962, 1966-1969, undated (Box 35, Folder 837)
  - Ingalls, M. S., 1940-1942 (Box 35, Folder 838)
  - Ingalls, Theodore H., 1946, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 839)
  - Ingraham, Franc, 1950, 1957, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 840)
  - Institut de France. Académie des Sciences, 1966, 1970-1973, undated (Box 35, Folder 841)
  - Institutum Divi Thomae Foundation, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 842)
  - Interferon, 1961-1967 (Box 35, Folder 843)
  - Interferon Information Exchange Group, 1964, undated (Box 35, Folder 844)
  - International Children's Center: seminar on hepatitis
    - Correspondence, 1969-1971, undated (Box 35, Folder 845-846)
    - Papers A-C, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 847)
    - Papers D-O, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 848)
    - Papers P-Z, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 849)
  - International Conference on Lung Tumours in Animals, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 850)
  - International Congress of Microbiology, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 851)
  - International Congress of Pediatrics, 1955, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 852)
  - International Congresses on Tropical Medicine and Malaria, 1957-1958 (Box 35, Folder 853)
  - International Journal of Cancer, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 854)
  - International Journal of Environmental Studies, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 855)
  - International Organization for Justice and Development, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 856)
  - International Phage Symposium, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 857)
  - International Poliomyelitis Congress
    See: box 74, folders 1641-1644
  - International Review of Experimental Pathology, 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 858)
  - International Science Foundation, 1970-1971, undated (Box 36, Folder 859)
  - International Union Against Cancer, 1968, undated (Box 36, Folder 860)
  - International Virus Nomenclature Committee. Virus subcommittee, 1958 (Box 36, Folder 861)
  - Interscience Conference on Antimicrobial Agents and Chemotherapy, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 862)
  - Interurban Clinical Club, 1960, undated (Box 36, Folder 863)
  - Invitations, 1947-1962 (Box 36, Folder 864-876)
  - Invitations, 1963-1975, undated (Box 37, Folder 877-886)
  - Irvine, Alexander R., 1962-1963, undated (Box 37, Folder 887)
  - Irwin, M. R., 1946 (Box 37, Folder 888)
  - Issacs, Alick, 1953-1954, 1959-1965 (Box 37, Folder 889)
  - J. A. Ewing and McDonald, Inc., 1941 (Box 37, Folder 890)
  - Jack, Ian, 1963, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 891)
  - Jacka, Cyril Keith, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 892)
  - Jackson, George Gee, 1962-1963 (Box 37, Folder 893)
  - Jackson Laboratory, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 894)
  - Jager, B. V., 1947-1948 (Box 37, Folder 895)
  - Janeway, Charles A., 1942, 1946-1953 (Box 38, Folder 896)
  - Janeway, Charles A., 1954-1964, 1967-1973, undated (Box 38, Folder 897)
    See also: box 26, folder 650
  - Japanese visitors: correspondence, 1951-1956, 1959-1970, undated (Box 38, Folder 898)
  - Jawetz, Ernest, 1948, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 899)
  - Jefferson Medical College, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 900)
  - Jenner Trust, 1966-1974, 1981, 1986, undated (Box 38, Folder 901)
  - Jennings, Brewster, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 902)
  - Jimmy Fund building, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 903)
  - John F. Enders Symposium on Current Topics in Human Virology, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 904)
  - John Wiley and Sons, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 905)
  - Johns Hopkins University. School of Medicine, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 906)
  - Johnson, Harald N., 1963 (Box 38, Folder 907)
  - Johnson, Kenneth P., 1972 (Box 38, Folder 908)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B.: inauguration, 1964-1965 (Box 38, Folder 909)
  - Joncas, Jean, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 910)
  - Jones, Oswald, 1963-1964 (Box 38, Folder 911)
  - Journal of Bacteriology, 1946-1951, 1964-1965 (Box 38, Folder 912)
  - Journal of Bacteriology, 1966, undated (Box 38, Folder 913)
  - Journal of Cancer, 1965-1966, undated (Box 38, Folder 914)
  - Journal of Cellular and Comparative Physiology, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 915)